Finding Aid for the Ronald Jacobs Papers PASC.0355
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ronald Jacobs papers
1961-1971
UCLA Library Special Collections
Jacobs, Ronald
PASC.0355
22.0 Linear Feet (45 boxes)
Ronald (Ronnie) Jacobs was involved in many television series, such as 1960s shows The Dick Van Dyke Show, The Andy Griffith Show, That Girl, and The Mod Squad. The collection consists of related to Jacobs' career.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ronald Jacobs, 2011 and 2012.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9967701983606533
Biographical History
Ronald Nicholas Jacobs (Ronnie) was born November 3, 1934 in Toledo, OH. He moved to Los Angeles, CA to attend UCLA where he received a BA in 1956. He first worked as a production assistant for producers Louis F. Edelman and Sheldon Leonard. Over his career he worked as an associate producer, production supervisor, production executive, director, producer, and executive producer. He was associated with companies such as Daisy Productions, Calvada Productions, Mayberry Productions, Mirisch/Rich Productions, Thomas/Spelling Productions, T & L Productions, and Independent Creative Artists Pictures. He also served as Executive in Charge of Production, for the Danny Thomas and Sheldon Leonard companies.
Jacobs was involved with numerous popular television productions including The Andy Griffith Show, The Danny Thomas Show, The Dick Van Dyke Show, Gomer Pyle U.S.M.C., I Spy, The Mod Squad, and That Girl. Jacobs also produced a number of feature films, including On the Right Track (1981), Jimmy the Kid (1982), Land of the Free (1998), and Running Red (1999).
Jacobs is a member of the Academy of Television Arts & Sciences, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, and the Directors Guild of America, and has been a judge for the Emmy Awards, Ace Cable Awards, and the Nicholl Fellowship Screenwriting Awards.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of producer Ronnie Jacobs. The bulk of the collection are script files representing 1960s television series including The Andy Griffith Show (1963-1969), The Bill Dana Show (1963-1964), The Dick Van Dyke Show (1961-1963, 1966), Gomer Pyle U.S.M.C. (1964-1967, 1969), The Joey Bishop Show (1962-1964), I Spy (1964-1967), The Mod Squad (1968-1971), That Girl (1966-1970), and others. Also included are a small number of scripts documenting Danny Thomas specials and Thomas/Spelling Productions made-for-TV movies. The television scripts document the careers of many entertainment writers, including Carl Reiner, Garry Marshall, Iz Elinson, and Ruth Brooks Flippen. Additionally, there is small amount of production information, correspondence, photographs and clippings.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by project title.
Television producers and directors -- Archives.; Jacobs, Ronald--Archives.
- Thomas/Spelling Productions
  - Corporal Crocker annotated script, circa 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Scope and Contents
    Writers: Margolin, Stuart
  - Over-the-Hill Gang (The) script, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Writers: Brewer, Jameson
  - Strangers in the Night annotated script, 1969 February 4 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Writers: Lakso, Edward J.; Roberts, Stanley
  - Wake Me When the War's Over script, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Writers: Peppiatt, Frank; Aylesworth, John
- Andy Griffith Show (The)
  - Andy and Opie's Pal - script, 1963 Oct 21 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    General note
    Writers: Bullock, Harvey
  - Andy Saves Gomer - script, 1963 Jan 13 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Andy's Baby - script (2 copies), 1969 Jul 11 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Writers: Rogers, Roswell
  - Andy's English Valet - script, 1963 Jan 24 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Andy's Investment - script, 1967 Sep 14 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Writers: Morris, Michael; Jacobs, Seaman
  - Andy's Rival - revised script, 1965 Jul 15 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Writers: Marks, Laurence
  - Andy's Trip to Raleigh - script, 1967 Jul 24 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Writers: Bonnaduce, Joe
  - Andy's Vacation - script, 1963 Dec 18 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Writers: Fritzell, Jim; Greenbaum, Everett
  - Aunt Bee and the Lecturer - script, 1967 Sep 6 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Aunt Bee Learns to Drive - revised script, 1965 Dec 9 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Writers: Elinson, Jack
  - Aunt Bee on TV - revised script, 1965 Jul 28 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Writers: Freeman, Fred; Cohen, Lawrence J.
  - Aunt Bee Takes a Job - revised script, 1965 Sep 23 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Writers: Idelson, Bill; Bobrick, Sam
  - Aunt Bee the Crusader - script, 1963 Oct 28 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Writers: Whedon, John
  - Aunt Bee the Juror - script, 1967 Jun 7 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Writers: Wilson, Kent
  - Aunt Bee, the Swinger - revised script, 1965 Jun 24 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Aunt Bee's Big Moment - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Writers: Bensfield, Dick; Grant, Perry
  - Aunt Bee's Big Moment - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Aunt Bee's Cousin - script, 1967 Oct 6 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Aunt Bee's Medicine Man - revised script, 1963 Jan 24 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Baby in the House (A) - revised script, 1966 Jan 11 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Back to Nature - script, 1964 Mar 19 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Bargain Day - script, 1964 Jan 20 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Barney and the Cave Rescue - script, 1963 Oct 14 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Barney and Thelma Lou, Phfftt - revised script, 1964 Mar 9 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Barney Hosts a Summit Meeting - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Writers: Ruben, Aaron
  - Barney's First Car - revised script, 1963 Feb 14 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Barney's Sidecar - script, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Battle of Mayberry (The) - revised script, 1966 Feb 17 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Writers: David, Paul; Greene, John L.
  - Bazaar (The) - revised script, 1965 Jul 9 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Writers: Joelson, Ben; Baer, Art
  - Big House (The) -script, 1963 Mar 20 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Black Day for Mayberry (A) - revised script, 1963 Aug 19 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Briscoe Declares for Aunt Bee - script, 1963 Jun 24 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cannon (The) - revised script, 1965 Sep 28 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Church Benefactor (The) - script, 1967 Nov 7 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Writers: Dennis, Robert C.; Barret, Earl
  - Church Organ - revised script, 1965 Oct 22 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Writers: Wayne, Paul
  - Citizen's Arrest - revised script, 1963 Sep 23 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - County Clerk (The) - revised script, 1966 Jan 18 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Darlings Are Coming (The) - revised script, 1963 Jan 31 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Date for Gomer (A) - script, 1963 Sep 16 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Deal is a Deal (A) - revised script, 1964 Feb 6 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Divorce - Mountain Style - script, 1964 Jan 29 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Dogs, Dogs, Dogs - revised script, 1963 Mar 12 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Eat Your Heart Out - revised script, 1965 Dec 31 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Writers: Baer, Art; Joelson, Ben
  - Emmett's Anniversary - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Writers: Grant, Perry; Bensfield, Richard
  - Emmett's Brother-In-Law - script, 1967 Oct 26 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Writers: Brooks, James L.
  - Ernest T. Bass Joins the Army - revised script, 1963 Aug 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Foster Lady (The) - revised script, 1966 Feb 9 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Writers: Elinson, Jack; Elinson, Iz
  - Fun Girls (The) - script, 1964 Feb 10 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Girl for Goober (A) - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Writers: Ross, Bob; Howard, Bruce
  - Girl Shy - revised script, 1965 Oct 11 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Gomer Pyle U.S.M.C. - script, 1963 Oct 4 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Gomer, the House Guest - script, 1965 Jul 8 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Goober and the Telephone Girl - script, 1969 Jun 9 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Writers: Grant, Perry; Bensfield, Dick
  - Goober Goes to the Auto Show - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Writers: Bonaduce, Joseph
  - Goober, the Executive - script, 1967 Jun 22 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Goober's Brother - script, 1969 Jun 12 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Writers: McGreevey, John
  - Goober's Replacement - revised script, 1966 Feb 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Writers: Dreben, Stan; Merrill, Howard
  - Gypsies (The) - revised script, 1966 Jan 7 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Writers: MacLane, Roland
  - Haunted House (The) -revised script, 1963 Jul22 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Helen's Past - script, 1968 Jan 5 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Writers: Tibbles, Doug
  - Hollywood Party (The) - revised script, 1965 Aug 19 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Writers: Cohen, Lawrence J.; Freeman, Fred
  - Hot Rod Otis - revised script, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Howard and Millie - script, 1967 Sep 29 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Howard the Poet - script (2 copies), 1969 Jun 17 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Howard, the Bowler - revised script, 1967 Jul 11 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Howard's Main Event - script, 1967 Jun 29 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Howard's New Life - script, 1967 Oct 12 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Legend of Barney Fife (The) - revised script, 1965 Nov 16 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Look, Paw, I'm Dancing - revised script, 1965 Dec 14 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Writers: Starr, Ben
  - Lost and Found - revised script, 1965 Nov 22 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Writers: Greene, John L.; David, Paul
  - Malcolm at the Crossroads - revised script, 1965 Jul22 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Man's Best Friend (A) - script, 1965 Aug 23 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mayberry Chef (The) - script, 1967 Oct 31 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mayberry Elects a Sheriff - script, 1963 Feb 5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Writers: James, Ed; Jacobs, Seaman
  - Mayberry R.F.D. - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Writers: Ross, Bob
  - Millie the Model - script, 1969 Jun 25 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Writers: Styler, Burt
  - My Fair Ernest T. Bass - script, 1963 Nov 18 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Opie and his Merry Men - revised script, 1963 Oct 2 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Opie and Mike - script, 1968 Feb 5 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Writers: Tibbles, Doug; Ross, Bob
  - Opie Steps Up in Class - script, 1967 Jul 18 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Opie the Birdman - revised script, 1963 Aug 16 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Opie's Drug Store Job - script, 1967 Nov 8 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Opie's First Love - revised script, 1967 Jun 15 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Writers: Tibbles, Doub
  - Opie's Group - revised script, 1967 Aug 17 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Opie's Ill-Gotten Gain - revised script, 1963 Sep 6 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Opie's Job - revised script, 1965 Jul 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Otis, the Artist - revised script, 1965 Nov 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Prisoner of Love - script, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Return of Barney Fife (The) - revised script, 1965 Nov 8 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Writers: Bobrick, Sam; Idelson, Bill
  - Return of Malcolm Merriwether (The) - revised script, 1964 Feb 27 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rivals (The) - script, 1963 Feb 28 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rumor (The) - script pages, 1964 Feb 28 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sam for Town Council - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Saving Morelli's - script, 1969 Jul 10 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Writers: Ross, Bob; West, Paul
  - Sermon for Today (The) - revised script, 1963 Aug 9 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Shoplifters (The) revised script, 1963 Dec 18 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Singer in Town (A) - revised script, 1966 Feb 23 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Song Festers (The) - script, 1963 Nov 20 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Suppose Andy Gets Sick - script, 1967 Sep 21 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Writers: Raymond, Jack
  - Tape Recorder, (The) - script, 1967 Aug 10 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Taylors in Hollywood (The) - revised script, 1965 Aug 11 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Trip to Mexico (A) - revised script, 1967 Aug 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Up in Barney's Room - script, 1963 Sep 12 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Warning from Warren (A) - revised script, 1965 Aug 26 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Wedding (The) - script, no date (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Writers: Bonaduce, Joe
  - Wife for Andy (A) - script, 1963 Mar 7 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Writers: Ruben Aaron
  - Wyatt Earp Ride Again - revised script, 1965 Dec 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Bill Dana Show (The)
  - Bank Hold-Up (The) - script, 1963 Aug 12 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Writers: Elinson, Jack; Stewart, Charles
  - Beauty and the Baby (The) - script, 1963 Oct 7 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Writers: Marshall, Garry; Belson, Jerry
  - Beauty and the Beast - script, 1963 Sep 24 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Beauty and the Bellhop - revised script, 1964 Nov 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Writers: O'Brien, Bob
  - Blood from Two Turnips - script, no date (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Writers: Singer, Ray; Chevillat, Dick
  - Brat (The) - script, 1963 Jun 27 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Writers: Keller, Sheldon; Merrill, Howard
  - Court Jester (The) - revised script, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Writers: Ostroff, Howard
  - Danny Thomas, I Love You - script, 1964 Aug 11 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Writers: Belson, Jerry; Marshall, Garry
  - Eddie Gets Fired - script, 1963 Oct 9 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Writers: Fox, Fred S.; Elinson, Iz
  - Essay (The) - script, no date (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Glick the Strong Man - revised script, 1964 Oct 13 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Writers: Ragaway, Martin A.
  - Hiring of Jose (The) - script, 1964 Jan 20 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Hot Dog Caper (The) - script, 1963 Jan 6 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hot Dog Caper (The) - script, 1964 Jan 27 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Hypnotist (The) - revised script, 1963 Jul 16 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Writers: Stewart, Charles; Elinson, Jack
  - Joe the Matchmaker - script, 1964 Jan 13 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Jose on the Ledge - script, 1964 Sep 1 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Jose Reigns - script, 1963 Dec 3 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Writers: Coons, Hannibal; Winkler, Harry
  - Jose Resigns - script, 1963 Jan 6 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Jose the Flower Thief - revised script, 1964 Jul 15 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Writers: Elinson, Iz; Elinson, Jack
  - Jose the Manager - script, 1963 Oct 9 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jose the Manager - script, 1963 Dec 9 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Jose the Old Man - script, 1964 Oct 20 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Writers: Allen, R. S.; Bullock, Harvey
  - Jose, the Agent - script, 1963 Aug 30 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Writers: Locke, Sam; Rapp, Joel
  - Jose, the Stockholder - script, 1963 Aug 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jose's Dream Girl - script, 1963 Nov 24 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Writers: Leeds, Howard
  - Jose's Dream Girl - script, 1963 Oct 18 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Jose's Four Amigos - script, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Jose's Four Amigos - script, 1963 Nov 8 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Jose's Inheritance - script, 1964 Sep 9 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Laughing Gas (The) - revised script, 1964 Jul 21 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Masquerade Party - revised script, 1963 Oct 24 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Writers: Persky, Bill; Denoff, Sam
  - Masquerade Party - script, 1963 Oct 28 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Masquerade Party - script, 1963 Sep 25 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Master of Disguise - script, 1964 Jan 21 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Master of Disguise - script, 1964 Feb 3 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mr. Phillips' Watch - script, 1963 Jun 28 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Writers: Leeds, Howard; Dana, Bill
  - Party in Suite 15 (The) - script, 1963 Dec 16 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Writers: Baer, Richard
  - Party in Suite 16 (The) - script, 1963 Nov 8 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Phillips the Lover - revised script, 1964 Sep 22 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Poker Game (The) - script, 1963 Sep 9 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Speak for Yourself, Jose - script, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Speak for Yourself, Jose - script, 1963 Nov 15 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Suggestion Box (The) - script, 1964 Aug 4 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Writers: Kleinschmitt, Carl; McRaven, Dale
  - Tip for Uncle Sam (A) - script, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Tonsils for Two - revised script, 1964 Oct 6 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - We'll Get You For This - script, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - What Elephant? - revised script, 1964 Jul 28 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Writers: Dana, Bill
  - You Gotta Have Heart - scripts, 1963 Apr 11 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    3 different versions
- Danny Thomas Hour (The)
  - America, I Love You - script, 1967 Nov 22 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Writers: Wedlock, Hugh Jr.; Manings, Allan
  - Cage (The) - revised script, 1967 Jul 27 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Writers: Boretz, Alvin; Kallis, Stanley
  - It's Greek to Me - revised script, 1967 Aug 15 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - My Friend Tony - revised script, 1967 Aug 17 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Writers: Goff, Ian; Roberts, Ben; Duff, Warren
  - Royal Follies of 1933 - script, 1967 Nov 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Writers: Keller, Sheldon
  - Sea World - revised script, 1967 Sep 5 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Danny Thomas Show (The)
  - Celebrating the 40th Anniversary of the Coconut Grove - revised script, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Appears to be a Danny Thomas Special
  - Danny Thomas Show (The) - script, 1965 Jan 13 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Writers: Elinson, Jack; Singer, Ray; Chevillat, Dick
  - Danny Thomas Show (The) - script, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Danny Thomas Show (The) (Danny Thomas Presents the Comics or What Makes People Laugh) - script, 1965 Sep 24 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Guys 'N Geishas - third draft script, 1966 Oct 12 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - My Home Town - annotated second draft script, 1965 Oct 15 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - My Home Town - first draft script, 1965 Oct 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - My Home Town - third draft script, 1965 Oct 23 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - The Wonderful World of Burlesque IV - script, 1967 Mar 29 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Danny Thomas Special (The)
  - Make Room for Grand-Daddy - annotated script, 1968 Sep 10 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Writers: Elinson, Jack; Paul, Norman
- Dick Van Dyke Show (The)
  - 4 1/2 - script, 1964 Jun 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - A Nice, Friendly Game of Cards - script, 1963 Sep 4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Writers: Chambers, Ernest
  - Alan Brady Show Goes to Jail (The) - script, 1964 Jun 9 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Alan Brady Show Presents (The) - script, 1963 Oct 28 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - And the Money Comes Rolling In - script, 1963 Jun 19 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Writers: Idelson, Bill
  - Antique Dealer (The) - script, 1963 Nov 7 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Bad Reception in Albany - script, 1965 Nov 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Beautiful Lady - script, 1964 Jan 24 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Big Max Calvada - script, 1963 Jul 22 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Writers: Denoff, Sam; Persky, Bill
  - Body and Soul - script, 1965 Oct 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Writers: Kleinschmitt, Carl; Mc Raven, Dale
  - Bottom of Mel Cooley's Heart (The) - script, 1965 Aug 10 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Boy #1 Versus Boy #2 - script, 1964 Nov 17 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Brave and the Backache (The) - revised script, 1963 Dec 13 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Buddy Sorrell - Man and Boy - script, 1965 Dec 27 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Bupkiss - script, no date (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Call Off the Hounds - script, 1964 Feb 12 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Captains Outrageous - revised script, 1963 Oct 4 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Case of the Pillow (The) - script, 1964 Sep 10 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Coast to Coast Big Mouth - script, 1965 May 24 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Courtship of Ritchie's Father (The) - revised script, 1963 Oct 28 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Curse of the Petrie People (The) - script, 1965 Jul 14 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Writers: McRaven, Dale; Kleinschmitt, Carl
  - Day in the Life of Alan Brady (A) - script, 1966 Jan 26 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Dear Mrs. Petrie, Your Husband is in Jail - script, 1964 Feb 10 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Don't Trip Over That Mountain - revised script, 1963 Jan 18 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Writers: Reiner, Carl
  - Draw Me a Pear - script, 1965 May 27 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Farewell to Writing (A) - script, 1965 Mar 23 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fifty-Two Forty-Five or Work - script, 1965 Sep 13 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Writers: Mittleman, Rick
  - Girls Will Be Boys - script, 1964 Dec 15 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Writers: Marshall; Belson
  - Go Tell the Birds and the Bees - script, 1965 Jul 15 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Great Petrie Fortune (The) - scripts (2 copies), 1965 May 6 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Writers: Chambers, Ernest; Burton, Jay
  - Gunslinger (The) - script, 1966 Feb 21 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Happy Birthday and Too Many More - script, 1963 Sep 9 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Honeymoons are for the Lucky - script, 1963 Dec 30 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - How to Spank a Star - script, 1963 May 9 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Writers: Curtis, Nat; Idelson, Bill
  - I Call on Rob Petrie - script, 1963 Oct 2 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - I Do Not Choose to Run - script, 1965 Oct 7 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - It Wouldn't Hurt Them to Give Us a Raise - script, 1964 Sep 10 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Writers: Burton, Jay; Chambers, Ernest
  - Lady and the Tiger and the Lawyer (The) - script, 1963 Nov 5 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Laura's Little Lie - script, 1963 Jul 23 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Life and Love of Hoe Coogan (The) - script, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Long Nights Journey into Day - script, 1965 Nov 5 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Making of a Councilman - script, 1965 Nov 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Man from 'Emperor' (The) - script, 1964 Jul 23 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Writers: Reiner, Carl; Persky, Bill; Denoff, Sam
  - Man From My Uncle - script, 1966 Feb 15 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Masterpiece (The) - script, 1963 Jul 24 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - My Husband is the Best One - script, 1963 Sep 6 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - My Neighbor's Husband's Other Life - script, 1964 Feb 19 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Never Battle on Saturday - script, 1965 Jan 14 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - No Rice At My Wedding - script, 1965 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Obnoxious, Offensive, Egomaniac, Etc. - script, 1966 Jan 3 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - October Eve - script, 1964 Jan 31 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Odd But True - script, no date (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Pen is Mightier than the Mouth (The) - revised script, 1963 Dec 27 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pink Pills and Purple Parents - script, 1964 Jul 22 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Plots Thicken (The) - script, 1964 Jan 15 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Quiz Show (The) - script, 1963 Oct 23 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Remember the Alimony - script, 1965 Dec 13 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Writers: Mc Raven, Dale; Kleinschmitt, Carl
  - Return of Edwin Carp (The) - script, 1964 Jan 27 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Romance, Roses and Rye Bread - revised script, 1964 Sep 3 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rusty and the Chorus Girl - script, 1964 Jan 29 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Scratch My Car and Die - revised script, 1964 Jan 6 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - See Rob Write, Write, Rob, Write - script, 1965 Jul 29 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Sound of the Trumpets of Conscience Falls Deafly on a Brain that Holds its Ears…Or Something Like That (The) - revised script, 1963 Oct 25 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Stretch Pants vs. Kid Schenk - script, 1964 Aug 18 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Talk to the Goat - script, 1966 Jan 7 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Teacher's Petrie - script, 1964 Mar 17 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - That's My Boy?? - script, 1963 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Three Letters From One Wife - script, 1964 Jul 17 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Turtles, Ties and Toreadors - revised script, 1963 Oct 18 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Ugliest Dog in the World (The) - script, 1965 May 3 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Uhny Uftz - script, 1965 May 24 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Uncle George - script, 1963 Apr 29 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Very Old Shoes, Very Old Rice - revised script, 1963 Aug 23 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Vigilante Ripped My Sports Coat (A) - script, 1964 Jul 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Viva Petrie - script, 1965 Jul 23 (Box 30, Folder 7)